Description & skills:

Frontend developer with extensive 9 years of experience and good understanding of related areas such as backend and design. I have worked on various types of websites and web applications. My core skills include HTML, CSS with preprocessors, Git, Javascript, Typescript, react.is, redux, CSS-in-JS tools. My key focus is on code maintainability/extendability. I'm always open to learning new tech or applying my recently acquired skills: React Native, Three.js or Svelte in a new project.

Experience:

04.2021 - 09.2023Onomy Protocol

Typescript, react.js, styled-components, D3.js

Developed responsive frontend from scratch for a presale token platform, web wallet, exchange, governance, bridge and other services within the web3 ecosystem.

This allowed the team to acquire \$11M+ of investments.

06.2017 - 04.2021BetterLegal

Typescript, nextis, react is, redux, redux-saga, styled-components, WebSocket, Stripe API

Solely developed a complete frontend for an internal CRM system that has given a possibility for managers to work with organizational data in real-time. Developed multiple company websites from landing pages to complex multi-form customer pages, integrated third-party services like Stripe payments, Zapier hooks, detailed analytics, etc. As a result company services sales grew in multiple times.

09.2014 - 06.2017Various small to large-size freelance projects

HTML, CSS, angular.js 1.x, knockout.js, ember.js, react.js, vue.js, WordPress, Webflow, jQuery & more

Completed more than 30~ projects including corporate websites, landing pages, UI for Electron-based video editing software, social media websites, email HTML templates, custom WordPress themes, Webflow websites, etc.

Education:

2010 – 2015	Master'r Degree in Information Security, Institution of IT and Control Systems, Belgorod State Tecnological University, Russia
2012 – 2015	Self-education with literature & online-platforms: Codeacademy, Coursera, Udemy, etc.

Other experience:

2008 – 2014	Worked as a part-time web-designer, completed around 120 freelance projects, including banners, website design, illustrations, pixel-art illustrations for gamedev.
2012 – 2014	PHP, Python, Ruby (& Ruby on Rails) non-commercial development.